[The Epoch of Miyu]
[미유시대]
[Episode 4]
[4화]
Sign this before you leave.
떠나기 전에 이것에 서명하세요.
You're really going to do this?
정말 이걸 할 건가요?
I've already signed it.
나는 이미 서명했습니다.
All that's left is your signature.
이제 남은 것은 서명뿐입니다.
I'll sign it when I get to the office.
사무실에 도착하면 서명하겠습니다.
I'll give it back to you tonight.
오늘 밤에 돌려드리겠습니다.
Lu Zhenzhen, why are you hiding?
Lu Zhenzhen, 왜 숨어 있습니까?
I'm not hiding.
나는 숨어 있지 않습니다.
I'm leaving out of respect for you.
나는 당신에 대한 존경심에서 떠나겠습니다.
Out of respect for me?
나를 존중해서?
That sounds like
그 말은
I'm the mistress.
나는 여주인이다.
You've had too much. Let's go back.
당신은 너무 많이 먹었습니다. 돌아가자.
I haven't even had a drink yet.
아직 한 잔도 안 마셨어요.
How am I drunk?
내가 어떻게 취한 거지?
Let go of me.
나를 놓아주세요.
Let go of me!
날 놔줘!
What's wrong with you?
왜 그래?
You're scared, aren't you, Nie Yucheng?
겁이 나지 않나요, Nie Yucheng?
That's you in the video, right?
영상에 나오는 사람이 바로 당신이군요, 그렇죠?
It's not some AI face swap, right?
AI 얼굴 교환이 아니죠?
It's me.
나야.
At a critical time like this,
지금과 같은 중요한 시기에
you're still making trouble for yourself?
아직도 혼자 문제를 일으키고 있나요?
Have you lost your mind?
정신을 잃었나요?
I don't know why she suddenly...
왜 갑자기...
Your promotion to Vice President
부사장으로 승진
was supposed to be announced this week.
이번주에 발표하기로 했는데요.
Now it's suddenly on hold,
이제 갑자기 보류되었네요
and the group is calling about it.
그리고 그룹은 그것에 대해 전화하고 있습니다.
You usually seem quite smart.
당신은 평소에 꽤 똑똑해 보이는데요.
How could you, at such a critical moment,
이렇게 중요한 순간에 어떻게
do such a stupid thing?
그런 멍청한 짓을 해?
You're just giving them ammo, aren't you?
당신은 그들에게 탄약을 주고 있는 것 뿐이죠, 그렇죠?
I don't know why
왜인지 모르겠어
things turned out like this.
상황이 이렇게 됐어요.
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
죄송합니다. 나는 틀렸다.
Go back right now and sort this out.
지금 당장 돌아가서 정리하세요.
Deal with your personal scandals.
개인적인 스캔들을 처리하십시오.
Stop messing around.
장난하지 마세요.
At the corporate group,
기업그룹에서는
I've said all the good things I could for you.
좋은 말은 다 했는데 나는 당신을 위해 할 수 있습니다.
But now that this matter has spread,
하지만 이제 이 문제가 확산되었으니
your promotion will definitely be delayed.
당신의 승진은 확실히 지연될 거예요.
Whether you get it in the end depends on your luck.
결국 얻게 되든 말든 당신의 운에 달려있습니다.
I'll deal with it immediately.
즉시 처리하겠습니다.
Thank you, Mr. Hu.
감사합니다, 후씨.
[Divorce Agreement]
[이혼합의서]
[Husband's fingerprint] [Wife's fingerprint] [Xu Miyu]
[남편의 지문] [아내의 지문] [쉬미유]
Why didn't you sign it?
왜 서명하지 않았나요?
I'm sorry, Miyu.
미안해, 미유.
I went too far that day.
그날 나는 너무 멀리 갔다.
I didn't really mean it,
정말 그런 뜻은 아니었어요,
but I hurt you in a moment of impulse.
하지만 순간 충동으로 당신에게 상처를 입혔습니다.
I hope you can forgive me.
당신이 나를 용서할 수 있기를 바랍니다.
I really don't want a divorce.
저는 정말 이혼하고 싶지 않아요.
Miyu,
미유,
I love you.
사랑해요.
I swear to you,
맹세해요
this time,
이번에는
I will make a clean break with Lu Zhenzhen.
깔끔하게 휴식을 취하겠습니다 루 젠젠과 함께.
I won't do anything to hurt you.
나는 당신을 다치게 하는 어떤 짓도 하지 않을 것입니다.
Please believe me.
저를 믿으세요.
Do you not want a divorce,
이혼을 원하지 않으세요
or do you just not want one right now?
아니면 지금 당장은 원하지 않는 거야?
What do you mean by that?
그게 무슨 뜻이에요?
I heard
들었어
your promotion to vice president got delayed.
당신의 프로모션 부사장님이 늦어졌습니다.
Are you waiting until after your promotion
승진이 끝날 때까지 기다리고 있나요
to finalize the divorce?
이혼을 마무리하려고?
You can't be serious, Xu Miyu.
진지하게 얘기하면 안 돼요, 쉬미유.
Do you really hate me that much?
너 정말 내가 그렇게 싫어?
Are you just bent on ruining my career?
내 경력을 망치려고 작정한 거야?
Anyway,
어쨌든,
we were husband and wife.
우리는 남편과 아내였습니다.
You turn against me just like that.
당신은 그렇게 나에게 반대합니다.
Don't you care about our past at all?
우리 과거에 전혀 관심이 없나요?
You are exaggerating, Nie Yucheng.
과장하는군요, Nie Yucheng.
Me,
나
ruin your future?
미래를 망쳐?
At most, I can delay it for a year or so.
기껏해야 1년 정도 미룰 수 있습니다.
As for the past you mentioned,
당신이 언급한 과거에 대해서는
after 10 years of marriage,
결혼한 지 10년 만에
I'm the one who truly has no way out.
나는 정말 탈출구가 없는 사람이다.
If I really take another step back,
내가 정말로 한 발 더 뒤로 물러난다면,
then I would really become
그러면 난 정말
the parasite you called me.
당신이 나를 불렀던 기생충.
Living off the job you gave me
당신이 나에게 준 일을 하며 살아가고
without any dignity.
품위도 없이.
Every day feels like having
매일매일 기분이 좋아
a fly stuck in my throat,
목에 파리가 걸렸어
forcing me to endure your acting
나에게 네 연기를 참도록 강요했어
and your lies.
그리고 당신의 거짓말.
Enough, Xu Miyu.
그만해, 쉬미유.
Is living with me that unbearable?
나랑 같이 사는 게 그렇게 견디기 힘든 걸까?
Yes.
예.
Fine.
괜찮은.
You want a divorce?
이혼을 원하시나요?
I agree!
동의합니다!
As for the family property,
가족 재산의 경우
you get the house and the car.
집과 차를 가져오세요.
We split the savings in half.
우리는 저축액을 절반으로 나누었습니다.
Do you agree?
동의하시나요?
The house was bought by my parents before we got married,
집은 샀어요 우리가 결혼하기 전에 부모님이 보내주신
so it definitely goes back to them.
그래서 그것은 확실히 그들에게 돌아갑니다.
The car was bought after we got married,
그 차는 우리가 결혼한 후에 샀어요,
but you don't know how to drive.
하지만 당신은 운전하는 방법을 모릅니다.
If we sell it,
팔면
it won't be worth much.
별로 가치가 없을 겁니다.
So the car belongs to me.
그러니 그 차는 내 것입니다.
Of course,
물론이죠,
you can use it if you need to.
필요한 경우 사용할 수 있습니다.
As for the savings,
절감액에 관해서는
you manage all the money at home.
당신은 집에서 모든 돈을 관리합니다.
You have my salary card.
당신은 내 급여 카드를 가지고 있습니다.
I'm not talking about your salary.
나는 당신의 급여에 대해 말하는 것이 아닙니다.
I mean savings.
저축을 의미합니다.
I don't have any savings.
저는 저축한 돈이 없습니다.
You have my salary card.
당신은 내 급여 카드를 가지고 있습니다.
You manage all the living expenses.
생활비를 모두 관리해 드립니다.
You know it best.
당신이 가장 잘 알고 있습니다.
The monthly utility bills, living expenses,
월별 공공요금, 생활비,
traveling a few times a year,
1년에 몇 번씩 여행을 가거나,
and various subsidies for your family:
그리고 가족을 위한 다양한 보조금:
your parents, your sister, and your brother-in-law.
너의 부모님, 너의 여동생, 그리고 당신의 처남.
-And travel... -What about the 150,000 Minghui borrowed?
-그리고 여행도... - 빌린 15만 명휘는 어떤가요?
That should be considered our savings.
그것은 우리의 저축으로 간주되어야 합니다.
Half of it should be mine.
그 절반은 내 것이 되어야 한다.
You know about that money.
당신은 그 돈에 대해 알고 있습니다.
It was given to the hospital,
병원에 전달됐어요
and it's impossible to get it back.
그리고 그것을 되돌리는 것은 불가능합니다.
I don't have any extra money.
나는 여분의 돈이 없습니다.
How about this?
이건 어때요?
When I have a bit more money,
돈이 좀 더 생기면
I will transfer your half of the 75,000
75,000 중 절반을 양도해 드리겠습니다
to you in installments.
할부로 당신에게.
Nie Yucheng,
니 유쳉,
you're really broke.
당신은 정말 파산했습니다.
It seems I really drained you over these 10 years.
내가 널 정말 지치게 만든 것 같아 이 10년 동안.
Then what is this?
그럼 이건 뭐죠?
[Project Investment Certificate]
[프로젝트 투자 증명서]
[Investor Information; Investor Name: Nie Yucheng]
[투자자정보; 투자자 이름: Nie Yucheng]
[Project information; Project name: Blue-chip Stock Investment]
[프로젝트 정보; 프로젝트 이름: 우량주식투자]
[Source of Funds] [Breakdown of Fund Usage]
[자금 출처] [자금 사용 내역]
This money is for my investments.
이 돈은 내 투자를 위한 것입니다.
I originally thought that if
나는 원래
we were to have a child,
우리는 아이를 가질 예정이었어
we could buy a house in a good school district.
우리는 집을 살 수 있었어 좋은 학군에서.
I'm sorry
미안해요
for letting you down.
당신을 실망시켰기 때문입니다.
I'm telling the truth.
나는 진실을 말하고 있습니다.
I didn't mean to hide it from you.
나는 당신에게 그것을 숨길 생각이 아니 었습니다.
I was thinking that when this investment matures
그때 생각하고 있었는데 이 투자는 성숙해졌어
and makes money,
그리고 돈을 벌고
I'd give you a surprise.
나는 당신에게 놀라움을 줄 것입니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
Then according to the terms,
그런 다음 용어에 따라
when it matures,
성숙해지면
we will split the principal and interest equally.
우리는 교장을 나눌 것입니다 그리고 이자는 균등하다.
Sign here if there's no problem.
문제가 없다면 여기에 서명하세요.
Xu Miyu,
쉬 미유,
you really impress me.
당신은 나에게 정말 깊은 인상을 줬어요.
You investigated me behind my back, didn't you?
당신은 나를 조사했습니다 내 뒤에서, 그렇지?
For all these years,
지난 몇 년 동안
did you love me,
나를 사랑했나요
or did you love my money?
아니면 내 돈을 사랑했나요?
I should be the one asking that question.
그 질문을 하는 사람은 바로 나여야 한다.
For all these years,
지난 몇 년 동안
did you love me,
나를 사랑했나요
or did you love my selfless devotion?
아니면 내 사심 없는 헌신을 사랑했나요?
Wait, what do you mean?
잠깐, 무슨 말이에요?
I mean that these 4 million
내 말은 이 400만 명
might not be able to
might not be able to
buy back my lost 10 years of youth,
못할 수도 있어
but at least it can save me some dignity
잃어버린 10년의 젊음을 되찾아주세요
and confidence.
하지만 적어도 그건 내 존엄성을 좀 지켜줄 수 있어
Sign it.
그리고 자신감.
What's the rush?
서명하세요.
Do you want to divorce me so badly?
서두르는 이유는 무엇입니까?
Do you hate me that much?
나한테 그렇게까지 이혼하고 싶은 거야?
Always talking about yourself...
내가 그렇게 싫어?
All you ever think about is yourself.
항상 자신에 대해 이야기합니다...
You flatter yourself, Nie Yucheng.
당신이 생각하는 모든 것은 당신 자신뿐입니다.
I'm not divorcing for you.
당신은 자신을 칭찬합니다, Nie Yucheng.
I'm doing it for myself.
나는 당신을 위해 이혼하지 않습니다.
I have wasted
나는 나 자신을 위해 그것을하고 있습니다.
too much on you.
낭비했어
I don't want to waste another second.
당신에게 너무 많은 것입니다.
Sign it.
나는 더 이상 시간을 낭비하고 싶지 않습니다.
[Husband's fingerprint: Nie Yucheng]
서명하세요.
You're free.
[남편 지문 : Nie Yucheng]
Enjoy your life.
당신은 자유입니다.
I'd like to see what you can achieve.
당신의 인생을 즐기십시오.
[Husband's fingerprint: Nie Yucheng]
나는 당신이 무엇을 성취할 수 있는지 보고 싶습니다.
Thank you.
[남편 지문 : Nie Yucheng]
As we can see,
감사합니다.
there are some problems here.
보시다시피,
You have to think.
여기에 몇 가지 문제가 있습니다.
You can go now.
당신은 생각해야합니다.
Of course.
이제 가셔도 됩니다.
Are you alright?
물론.
Landi Horse cheated us.
괜찮으세요?
Their chairman
Landi Horse가 우리를 속였습니다.
signed a contract with the Future Group just yesterday.
회장
We are too late.
계약을 체결했다 바로 어제 퓨처그룹과 함께.
You mean like yesterday?
우리는 너무 늦었어요.
Yeah,
어제처럼 말이에요?
just yesterday.
응,
I need to go find the chairman.
바로 어제요.
Yes.
회장님을 찾으러 가야 해요.
I think it's too late to see him now.
예.
The chairman was on a meditation retreat yesterday.
지금 그를 만나기에는 너무 늦은 것 같아요.
There's no way he would have taken any meetings.
회장님이 계셨는데 어제 명상 수련회.
You know what?
그 사람이 그럴 리가 없어 어떤 회의를 가졌습니다.
That news
그거 알아?
is probably just a bluff by Future Group.
그 소식
♪ Life is full of ♪
아마도 Future Group의 허세 일 것입니다.
♪ Countless crossroads ♪
♪ 인생은 ♪
[Graduation Certificate]
♪ 수많은 교차로 ♪
[General High School Graduation Certificate]
[졸업증명서]
♪ Chase joy too hard, and it slips away ♪
[일반 고등학교 졸업증명서]
[Education background: Hushi University]
♪ 기쁨을 너무 세게 쫓다 보면 어느새 사라져 버립니다 ♪
♪ All those confusions ♪
[학력 : 후시대학]
♪ No answers, no reasons ♪
♪ 그 모든 혼란 ♪
♪ Throwing ourselves into the tide of the unknown ♪
♪ 답변도 없고 이유도 없습니다 ♪
[Hotel environment]
♪ 몸을 던져 미지의 세계 속으로 ♪
[Positions at Star Vault Hotel]
[호텔 환경]
[Enjoying unparalleled working benefits]
[스타볼트호텔 채용정보]
[Travel bonus and benefits] [Recognition and reward]
[탁월한 업무 혜택을 누리세요]
♪ Knowing when to advance or retreat, yet still asleep ♪
[여행 보너스 및 혜택] [인정과 보상]
[Keep in touch]
♪ 전진할 때와 후퇴할 때를 아는 것, 아직 자고 있어요 ♪
♪ Rushing to ripen before our time ♪
[연락을 유지하세요]
[Xu Miyu] [Resume] [Upload Attachment]
♪ 시간이 오기 전에 익기 위해 서두르고 있습니다 ♪
[Attachment Management]
[쉬미유] [이력서] [첨부파일 업로드]
[Xu Miyu's personal resume]
[첨부파일 관리]
♪ Sighing at partings, who meets whom at which crossing ♪
[서미유 개인 이력서]
[Open]
♪ 이별에 한숨을 쉬며 어느 교차점에서 누가 누구를 만나는지 ♪
[Resume]
[열기]
[Upload Attachment]
[이력서]
[Xu Miyu]
[첨부파일 업로드]
[Personal Strengths: Positive and outgoing personality]
[쉬미유]
♪ Busy and restless ♪
[개인적인 장점: 긍정적이고 외향적인 성격]
[A strong sense of responsibility and team spirit]
♪ 바쁘고 불안해요 ♪
[Desired Position: Full-time]
[희망 포지션 : 정규직]
♪ No turning back, no stopping ♪
♪ 되돌릴 수도, 멈출 수도 없습니다 ♪
[Role experience] [Work experience]
[역할 체험] [직무 체험]
[Project experience]
[프로젝트 경험]
[Education: Hushi University, Bachelor's in Hotel Management]
[학력 : 후시대학교, 호텔경영학 학사]
♪ Our path—do you see it now ♪
♪ 우리의 길, 이제 보이나요 ♪
♪ Just lift your head, oh ♪
♪ 고개를 들어보세요, 오 ♪
♪ Don't look back ♪
♪ 뒤돌아보지 마세요 ♪
♪ I've already learned ♪
♪ 난 이미 배웠어요 ♪
[Seller: Ji Feng; Buyer: Nolan]
[판매자: Ji Feng; 구매자: 놀란]
♪ If it's not mine, I won't force it ♪
♪ 내 것이 아니라면 강요하지 않겠습니다 ♪
How did you do this?
어떻게 했나요?
We finally made it.
우리는 마침내 해냈습니다.
♪ No matter how you force it ♪
♪ 아무리 강요해도 ♪
[Seller: Ji Feng; Buyer: Nolan]
[판매자: Ji Feng; 구매자: 놀란]
♪ It'll only turn into a long, endless wait ♪
♪긴 이야기가 될 뿐입니다. 끝없는 기다림 ♪
Kenny.
케니.
First of all,
우선,
my congrats to you on signing this contract.
축하해요 이 계약서에 서명하면서.
♪ Waiting to make peace with myself ♪
♪ 나 자신과 평화를 이루기를 기다리고 있습니다 ♪
But
하지만
vast majority of the effort on signing this contract
대부분의 노력 이 계약에 서명하면서
♪ And waiting to meet someone again ♪
♪ 그리고 누군가를 다시 만나기를 기다리고 있어요 ♪
was made by me
내가 만든 거야
♪ Wave goodbye ♪
♪ 손을 흔들어 작별 인사 ♪
and my team.
그리고 내 팀.
Keep your contract.
계약을 유지하세요.
What?
무엇?
And your hotel.
그리고 당신의 호텔.
♪ Knowing when to advance or retreat, yet still asleep ♪
♪ 전진할 때와 후퇴할 때를 아는 것, 아직 자고 있어요 ♪
♪ Rushing to ripen before our time ♪
♪ 시간이 오기 전에 익기 위해 서두르고 있습니다 ♪
♪ Sighing at partings, who meets whom at which crossing ♪
♪ 이별에 한숨을 쉬며 어느 교차점에서 누가 누구를 만나는지 ♪
Kenny, hope to see you soon.
케니, 곧 뵙기를 바랍니다.
Goodbye.
안녕히 가세요.
♪ Busy and restless ♪
♪ 바쁘고 불안해요 ♪
♪ No turning back, no stopping ♪
♪ 되돌릴 수도, 멈출 수도 없습니다 ♪
♪ Our path—do you see it now ♪
♪ 우리의 길, 이제 보이나요 ♪
♪ Just lift your head, oh ♪
♪ 고개를 들어보세요, 오 ♪
♪ Don't look back ♪
♪ 뒤돌아보지 마세요 ♪
♪ I've already learned ♪
♪ 난 이미 배웠어요 ♪
♪ If it's not mine, I won't force it ♪
♪ 내 것이 아니라면 강요하지 않겠습니다 ♪
♪ No matter how you force it ♪
♪ 아무리 강요해도 ♪
♪ It'll only turn into a long, endless wait ♪
♪긴 이야기가 될 뿐입니다. 끝없는 기다림 ♪
♪ Waiting to make peace with myself ♪
♪ 나 자신과 평화를 이루기를 기다리고 있습니다 ♪
♪ And waiting to meet someone again ♪
♪ 그리고 누군가를 다시 만나기를 기다리고 있어요 ♪
♪ Wave goodbye ♪
♪ 손을 흔들어 작별 인사 ♪
Ms. Xu,
쉬 선생님,
Room 1819 is ready for you.
1819호실이 준비되어 있습니다.
[Purong Hotel]
[푸롱 호텔]
I don't want 1819.
나는 1819를 원하지 않는다.
Please change my room.
내 방 좀 바꿔주세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
Enjoy your stay.
즐거운 시간 보내세요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Good evening, ma'am.
안녕하세요, 부인.
This way, please.
이쪽으로 부탁드립니다.
Welcome.
환영.
Please come in.
들어오세요.
I'd like to order.
주문할게요.
Certainly, ma'am.
물론이죠, 부인.
To order, please dial...
주문하려면 전화를 걸어주세요...
I want Boston lobster.
보스턴 랍스터를 먹고 싶어요.
Boston lobster.
보스턴 랍스터.
And bluefin tuna,
그리고 참다랑어,
stir-fried sea snails,
바다 달팽이 볶음
and wine-marinated crab.
그리고 와인에 절인 게.
For one person,
1인의 경우,
this might be a bit too much.
이건 좀 과할 수도 있어요.
It's been exactly 10 years
정확히 10년이 지났어요
since I last had a proper seafood meal.
지난번에 제대로 된 해산물 식사를 한 이후로요.
I'm going to eat to my heart's content today.
나는 먹을거야 오늘은 마음이 편해요.
And give me a serving of ark shell.
그리고 방주 껍데기 한 접시 주세요.
What's going on?
무슨 일이야?
Never mind.
괜찮아요.
Haven't we seen enough of this?
우리는 이것을 충분히 보지 못했습니까?
F&B Department.
F&B 부문.
A guest on the executive floor is ordering.
이그제큐티브 플로어의 손님 주문 중입니다.
I used to think
난 생각하곤 했어
that giving all of myself
그건 나 자신을 모두 바치는 것
to another person
다른 사람에게
was also a form of self-realization.
그것은 또한 자기 실현의 한 형태였습니다.
Until one day I came to my senses
어느 날 정신을 차릴 때까지
and realized
그리고 깨달았어
that I had been treating myself so carelessly,
내가 그랬던 것 나 자신을 너무 부주의하게 대해서
losing myself further and further.
점점 더 나 자신을 잃어가고 있습니다.
Forget about the stomach-soothing meal.
배를 달래주는 식사는 잊어버리세요.
Let your mistress make it for you.
당신의 여주인이 당신을 위해 그것을 만들도록하십시오.
But now I'm going to pick myself up.
하지만 이제 나는 나 자신을 데리러 갈 것입니다.
Stop ordering her around,
그녀에게 명령하지 마세요.
stop criticizing her,
그녀를 비난하지 마세요
and let her do whatever she wants.
그리고 그녀가 원하는 것은 무엇이든 하게 해주세요.
I hope she can live
그 사람이 살 수 있었으면 좋겠어
every day for her own happiness.
자신의 행복을 위해 매일.
Xu Miyu,
쉬 미유,
good job.
잘했어요.
♪ That fleeting moment I tried to hold ♪
♪ 붙잡으려고 노력한 그 찰나의 순간 ♪
♪ Let it go when the glass runs dry ♪
♪ 유리잔이 마르면 놓아두세요 ♪
♪ Unfinished longings ♪
♪ 끝나지 않은 그리움 ♪
♪ Drift like fading embers ♪
♪ 사라져가는 불씨처럼 표류합니다 ♪
♪ Still longing for yesterday's glow ♪
♪ 아직도 어제의 빛을 그리워하고 있어요 ♪
♪ Yet sailing into the ocean's depths at night ♪
♪ 아직 항해 중 밤에는 바다 깊은 곳으로 ♪
♪ Questions without answers ♪
♪ 답이 없는 질문 ♪
♪ Let them go with the wind ♪
♪ 바람과 함께 보내주세요 ♪
♪ Let them go ♪
♪ 그들을 보내주세요 ♪
Hello?
안녕하세요?
Clean the room,
방을 청소해
now.
지금.
Hello,
안녕하세요,
room service.
룸서비스.
[October 31]
[10월 31일]
[Message]
[메시지]
[Ms. Xu Miyu, we regret to inform you that your profile
[여사. 쉬미유, 후회한다 당신의 프로필이
[is not the best fit for this role.]
[이 역할에 가장 적합하지 않습니다.]
[Hello, I'm very interested in the Housekeeping Supervisor position]
[안녕하세요. 정말 관심이 많아요. 하우스키핑 감독자 위치]
[(5-day workweek with 2 days off)...]
[(주 5일 근무, 2일 휴무)...]
[JD Cleaning Specialist — 8,000 RMB/month]
[JD 청소 전문가 — 8,000 RMB/월]
[Free training, stable orders]
[무료 교육, 안정적인 주문]
[JD Hiring Cleaning Specialists Urgently; 8,000 RMB/month]
[JD가 긴급하게 청소 전문가를 고용합니다; 8,000위안/월]
[Jobs assigned nearby, steady orders]
[근처에 배정된 일자리, 꾸준한 주문]
[Competition Analysis]
[경쟁 분석]
[Manting Art Hotel]
[맨팅 아트 호텔]
[Update on Your Application for the Assistant General Manager Position]
[귀하의 신청서 업데이트 차장직]
Hello.
안녕하세요.
I interviewed
인터뷰를 했어
at your hotel recently.
최근에 당신의 호텔에서.
My name is Xu Miyu.
제 이름은 쉬미유입니다.
I just received the rejection letter.
방금 거절 편지를 받았습니다.
I would like
나는 원한다
to explain a few things.
몇 가지를 설명하기 위해.
Could you give me another chance?
나에게 한 번 더 기회를 주실 수 있나요?
I am sorry, ma'am.
죄송해요, 부인.
The employee we hired has already started today.
우리가 고용한 직원 오늘 이미 시작되었습니다.
Please try other companies.
다른 회사를 이용해 보시기 바랍니다.
Goodbye.
안녕히 가세요.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Mr. Su.
수 씨.
What?
무엇?
The 8 million is gone?
800만은 없어졌나요?
The opposing lawyer sent me an investment report today.
상대변호사는 오늘 나에게 투자 보고서를 보냈습니다.
This project is currently suffering severe losses.
이 프로젝트는 현재 심각한 손실을 입고 있습니다.
Not only is there no profit,
이익이 없을 뿐만 아니라,
but there is also a debt of over 2 million.
하지만 빚도 있어요 2백만이 넘습니다.
Mr. Nie stated
Nie씨는
that he doesn't plan to split the debt with you.
그 사람은 계획하지 않는다고 당신과 빚을 나누기 위해.
He will bear it himself
그는 스스로 감당할 것이다
and wants to negotiate with you.
그리고 당신과 협상하고 싶어합니다.
This is definitely Nie Yucheng's trick.
이것은 확실히 Nie Yucheng의 속임수입니다.
He just wants to stall and not pay.
그는 단지 멈추고 돈을 지불하지 않기를 원합니다.
But his trick worked.
그러나 그의 트릭은 성공했습니다.
Why?
왜?
Because this amount was in the negative
이 금액이 마이너스였기 때문에
during your marriage.
결혼하는 동안.
Even if it turns into a profit later,
나중에 수익이 나더라도
according to the Marriage Law,
결혼법에 따르면,
since your marriage is already dissolved,
당신의 결혼은 이미 해산되었기 때문에
it will no longer be considered
더 이상 고려되지 않습니다
your joint property.
귀하의 공동 재산.
Which means
그 말은
he no longer has to split it with you.
그는 더 이상 당신과 그것을 나눌 필요가 없습니다.
Knowing Nie Yucheng,
Nie Yucheng을 아는 중,
he'd never make such a losing investment.
그는 결코 그렇게 손해보는 투자를 하지 않을 것이다.
He's obviously transferring his assets.
그는 분명히 자신의 자산을 양도하고 있습니다.
Can I sue him?
그를 고소할 수 있나요?
It will take time.
시간이 걸릴 것입니다.
We don't have enough evidence.
증거가 충분하지 않습니다.
Now is not the best time to sue.
지금은 소송을 제기할 최적의 시기가 아닙니다.
I'm not completely sure we can win.
나는 우리가 이길 수 있을지 완전히 확신하지 못한다.
I can find the evidence.
증거를 찾을 수 있어요.
And I can wait.
그리고 나는 기다릴 수 있다.
I must get this money.
이 돈은 꼭 받아야 해요.
Mr. Su, you have to help me.
수 씨, 저를 도와주셔야 해요.
Good morning, ma'am.
좋은 아침입니다, 부인.
Hello. I'd like to check out.
안녕하세요. 체크아웃하고 싶어요.
Okay.
좋아요.
Did you rest well last night,
어젯밤에 잘 쉬셨나요
Ms. Xu?
쉬씨?
It was fine.
괜찮았어요.
Your total comes
당신의 총액은 다음과 같습니다
to 6,680 yuan.
6,680위안.
Would you like to pay by phone or card?
전화로 결제하시겠습니까, 아니면 카드로 결제하시겠습니까?
6,680?
6,680?
Isn't your executive suite only 2,300?
귀하의 임원실은 2,300명에 불과하지 않습니까?
The alcohol in the room
방에 술이 있어
and the meals you ordered are charged separately.
그리고 주문한 음식 별도로 청구됩니다.
You ordered
주문하셨습니다
2,190 yuan worth of seafood
2,190위안 상당의 해산물
and 540 yuan worth of drinks,
그리고 540위안 상당의 음료수,
plus a 100 yuan room service fee.
게다가 룸서비스 비용 100위안이 추가됩니다.
Here is your itemized bill.
여기 항목별 청구서가 있습니다.
Then what's the other 1,550 for?
그럼 나머지 1,550개는 뭐예요?
You ruined 2 of our carpets
당신이 우리 카펫 2개를 망쳤어요
and a crystal ornament.
그리고 크리스탈 장식.
So...
그럼...
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
I forgot.
잊어버렸어요.
Ms. Xu.
쉬 씨.
So, will you pay by phone or card?
그럼 전화로 결제하실 건가요, 카드로 결제하실 건가요?
WeChat Pay.
위챗페이.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Welcome.
환영.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
It's okay.
괜찮아요.
Thank you for staying with us.
우리와 함께있어 주셔서 감사합니다.
[14 years ago]
[14년 전]
[Purong Hotel]
[푸롱 호텔]
Hello.
안녕하세요.
[Young Ji Feng]
[영지펑]
I'm the new intern starting today.
저는 오늘부터 신입사원입니다.
Where should I report?
어디에 신고해야 하나요?
Take the staff entrance.
직원 입구를 이용하세요.
It's right over there.
바로 저쪽에 있어요.
Okay, thank you.
알겠습니다. 감사합니다.
Welcome aboard,
탑승을 환영합니다.
new colleague.
새로운 동료.
The elevator is over there.
엘리베이터는 저기에 있어요.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Eighth floor?
8층?
Check-in.
체크인.
Hello, sir.
안녕하세요, 선생님.
Welcome.
환영.
Mr. Ji.
지 씨.
I see you booked our executive floor.
귀빈층을 예약하셨군요.
Would you like to check in early?
일찍 체크인하시겠습니까?
Yes.
예.
Then I suggest you sign up for our membership.
그럼 나는 당신에게 제안합니다 우리 회원가입을 하세요.
[Join as a VIP for RMB 50,000]
[RMB 50,000에 VIP로 가입하세요]
[and enjoy exclusive privileges]
[독점적인 특권을 누려보세요]
With a membership, you can check in early
회원이 되시면 일찍 체크인하실 수 있습니다
and enjoy a 20% discount
20% 할인 혜택을 누려보세요
at the Western and Chinese restaurants.
서양식 레스토랑과 중국식 레스토랑에서.
No, thanks.
아니요, 고마워요.
I just want to check in early.
그냥 일찍 체크인하고 싶어요.
You want me to spend 50,000 yuan?
50,000위안을 쓰길 원하시나요?
Check-in for non-members
비회원 체크인
starts at 2 PM.
오후 2시에 시작합니다.
I suggest you come back this afternoon.
오늘 오후에 다시 오시길 권합니다.
[Black Card VIP at Purong Hotel]
[푸롱호텔 블랙카드 VIP]
With this,
이것으로
can I check in early?
일찍 체크인할 수 있나요?
Yes, sir.
네, 선생님.
I'll handle it for you now.
지금은 제가 대신 처리해 드리겠습니다.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
I'll send it up right away.
바로 보내드리겠습니다.
It's done.
끝났습니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Thanks.
감사해요.
Cover for me.
나를 위해 커버해 주세요.
Mr. Ji.
지 씨.
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
You are a Black Card VIP guest of our hotel.
당신은 블랙카드 VIP입니다 우리 호텔의 손님.
The system just showed
시스템이 방금 보여줬어요
that you will be staying here for a long time.
당신이 여기에 머물 것이라고 오랫동안.
If you don't mind,
괜찮으시다면
I can show you around
주변을 안내해 드릴 수 있어요
to get familiar with the place.
그 장소에 익숙해지려고.
Would you like that?
그렇게 하시겠습니까?
Sure.
확신하는.
This way, please.
이쪽으로 부탁드립니다.
Our Purong Hotel
푸롱 호텔
has been established for nearly half a century.
설립되었습니다 거의 반세기 동안.
In Shanghai,
상하이에서는
it is a well-known, established 5-star hotel.
그것은 잘 알려진, 5성급 호텔을 설립했습니다.
On your right-hand side
오른쪽에
is our hotel's banquet hall.
저희 호텔의 연회장입니다.
It has hosted
It has hosted
a wide variety of business banquets.
다양한 비즈니스 연회.
[Young Ji Feng]
[영지펑]
It can accommodate
It can accommodate
around 200 people.
약 200명.
If you need it in the future,
앞으로도 필요하시면,
you can always
넌 언제든지 할 수 있어
contact our front office to make a reservation.
우리 프론트 오피스에 연락해 예약을 하려고.
Over the years, our Purong Hotel
수년에 걸쳐 우리 푸롱 호텔
has kept pace with the times.
시대에 발맞추어 왔습니다.
Both in terms of decor and cuisine,
장식과 요리 측면에서
it combines Chinese and Western elements.
그것은 중국과 서양의 요소를 결합합니다.
As for the dishes,
요리에 관해서는
we have a variety of flavors.
우리는 다양한 맛을 가지고 있습니다.
You can choose according to your preference.
당신은 선택할 수 있습니다 당신의 취향에 따라.
If you need to,
필요하다면,
you can also contact us for a reservation anytime.
당신은 또한 우리에게 연락할 수 있습니다 언제든지 예약하실 수 있습니다.
Here is our Western restaurant,
여기 서양식 레스토랑이 있습니다.
where you can
어디에서 할 수 있나요
taste delicacies from all over the world.
전 세계의 진미를 맛보세요.
Our newly introduced afternoon tea and desserts
우리가 새로 소개한 애프터눈 티와 디저트
are extremely delicious.
매우 맛있습니다.
If you have time,
시간이 있으면
you should come and try them.
와서 시험해 봐야 해.
What is that smell?
그 냄새는 무엇입니까?
What?
무엇?
I feel like
내 기분은
there's a very pungent smell here.
여기서는 아주 지독한 냄새가 나요.
Don't you smell it?
냄새 안 나나요?
It should be the smell of disinfectant.
소독약 냄새여야 합니다.
This smell is expected
이 냄새가 예상되는 것 같아요
during routine cleaning.
일상적인 청소 중.
This way, please.
이쪽으로 부탁드립니다.
Mr. Ji,
지 선생님,
this is our executive lounge.
이곳은 우리의 이그제큐티브 라운지입니다.
It is an exclusive space designed
설계된 전용 공간입니다
for our VIP guests on the executive floor,
귀빈층에 있는 VIP 손님들을 위해
providing exquisite dining
고급스러운 식사를 제공
and personalized service around the clock.
24시간 내내 맞춤형 서비스를 제공합니다.
If you're interested later,
나중에 관심이 있으시면
you can come and experience it.
오셔서 체험해 보실 수 있습니다.
So,
그래서,
Mr. Ji, are you satisfied with the tour?
지 선생님, 투어에 만족하시나요?
I'm curious
궁금해요
how Purong Hotel
어떻게 푸롱 호텔
keeps its guests now.
지금 손님을 유지하고 있습니다.
I'm sorry?
죄송합니다?
Your front desk staff is slack,
프론트 데스크 직원이 느슨해요,
and the hallways smell like disinfectant.
복도에서는 소독약 냄새가 나요.
After this tour you gave me,
이 투어가 끝난 후 당신은 나에게
do you think I'm satisfied?
내가 만족할 것 같아?
Mr. Ji.
지 씨.
I...
나는...
That's not what I meant.
내 말은 그런 뜻이 아니었어.
Mr. Ji,
지 선생님,
you're our distinguished Black Card VIP.
당신은 우리의 특별한 블랙카드 VIP입니다.
I'm your butler, Yin Xiang.
저는 당신의 집사 Yin Xiang입니다.
Feel free to contact me if you need anything.
저에게 연락 주시기 바랍니다 필요한 것이 있으면.
-Okay. Thank you. -Enjoy your stay.
-좋아요. 감사합니다. - 즐거운 시간 보내세요.
Well.
잘.
Let's go.
갑시다.
Is he crazy?
그 사람 미쳤나요?
We have a difficult Black Card VIP.
어려운 블랙카드 VIP가 있습니다.
His surname is Ji.
그의 성은 지(Ji)이다.
Everyone, be careful.
여러분, 조심하세요.
This is your future service standard
이것이 당신의 미래 서비스 표준입니다
and the service attitude you must uphold.
그리고 당신이 지켜야 할 서비스 태도.
Today is your first day on the job.
오늘은 직장에서의 첫 번째 날입니다.
I want you to listen carefully
잘 들어주셨으면 좋겠어요
to what I have to say next.
다음에 내가 할 말은.
In the future, no matter
앞으로는
which position you rotate to in the hotel,
which position you rotate to in the hotel,
you must firmly remember:
호텔에서 어느 위치로 회전하는지
Making guests feel at home
당신은 다음을 확실히 기억해야 합니다:
is the service tenet of our Purong Hotel.
손님들이 집에 있는 듯한 편안함을 느끼도록 하기
It might sound a bit cliché,
푸롱 호텔의 서비스 신조입니다.
but I believe
다소 진부하게 들릴 수도 있습니다.
it's the foundation of our hotel service.
하지만 난 믿어요
When a guest walks into the hotel,
이것이 우리 호텔 서비스의 기초입니다.
every part of our hotel
손님이 호텔에 들어오면
starts working for them.
우리 호텔의 모든 부분
We need to keenly perceive
그들을 위해 일하기 시작합니다.
every need of the guest
우리는 예리하게 인식해야 합니다
and cater to all their senses,
손님의 모든 필요
providing service more caring than being at home.
그들의 모든 감각을 충족시켜주죠
Purong Hotel was established
서비스 제공 집에 있는 것보다 더 배려심이 많다.
nearly half a century ago,
푸롱호텔 설립
and this is how we retain our guests.
거의 반세기 전,
In your future work,
이것이 우리가 손님을 유지하는 방법입니다.
I hope
향후 작업에서는
in every service,
그러길 바라요
you can understand
모든 서비스에서
the meaning of working in a hotel.
너는 이해할 수 있어
This is also the value
호텔에서 일하는 것의 의미.
that Purong provides you.
이것은 또한
[Hotel Manager] [Details]
푸롱이 제공하는 것입니다.
[Requirements: At least 5 years of experience in hotel management]
[호텔 지배인] [자세히]
[and operations. Base salary: 8,000 RMB + commission]
[요건 : 최소 5년 이상 호텔 경영 경험]
[Compensation & Benefitst]
[그리고 작전. 기본 급여: 8,000 RMB + 커미션]
[Salary Expectation (Monthly, RMB)]
[보상 및 혜택]
Here. Be careful.
오다.
Okay.
여기. 조심하세요.
Come.
좋아요.
The room might not be big,
오다.
but the location is great.
방은 크지 않을 수도 있어요
Transport is convenient.
하지만 위치는 훌륭합니다.
You step right out into the downtown area.
교통이 편리합니다.
And look, your bed is up here.
바로 시내 지역으로 나가시면 됩니다.
It's very private.
그리고 보세요, 당신의 침대는 여기 위에 있어요.
4,000 yuan a month.
매우 사적입니다.
It's really a bargain.
한 달에 4,000위안.
Can you make it a bit cheaper?
정말 특가네요.
How about this?
좀 더 저렴하게 해줄 수 있나요?
If you can
이건 어때요?
pay 6 months' rent at once,
가능하다면
I'll let you have it for 3,500 a month.
6개월치 집세를 한꺼번에 지불해
That saves you 3,000 in total.
한 달에 3,500원으로 해드립니다.
Okay.
총 3,000원을 절약할 수 있습니다.
Deal.
좋아요.
Great.
거래.
Here, scan my code.
엄청난.
[Loading]
여기, 내 코드를 스캔하세요.
[Payment to Individual: RMB 21,000]
[로드 중]
All right.
[개인 지급액: RMB 21,000]
Keep this key.
괜찮은.
And you can
이 열쇠를 보관하세요.
tidy up by yourself.
그리고 당신은
I'll get going now.
스스로 정리하세요.
Alright.
이제 가겠습니다.
Thank you.
괜찮은.
Bye.
감사합니다.
[My balance: 1,407 yuan]
안녕.
Hello.
[내 잔액: 1,407위안]
Yes, it's me.
안녕하세요.
I submitted the resume.
네, 나예요.
Okay.
이력서를 제출했습니다.
I'll be right there.
좋아요.
[Xiaoma Hotel]
바로 거기 갈게요.
I remember
[샤오마 호텔]
your resume.
기억나네
After being a housewife for 10 years,
10년 동안 주부 생활을 한 후,
do you think you are up to this job?
당신이 이 일을 할 수 있을 것 같나요?
Well, ma'am,
음, 부인,
although I don't have much work experience,
비록 나는 없지만 많은 업무 경험이 있어요
I graduated from Hushi University
나는 후시대학교를 졸업했다
with a major in hotel management.
호텔경영을 전공한 사람.
When it comes to handling practical matters,
그럴 때 실질적인 문제를 처리하고
I also have some experience.
저도 경험이 좀 있어요.
For instance, I handle our family's utility bills
예를 들어, 나는 처리합니다 우리 가족의 공과금
and commercial insurance contracts...
그리고 상업 보험 계약...
We are a hotel.
우리는 호텔입니다.
Do you understand the current hotel business?
이해하셨나요? 현재 호텔 사업은요?
My husband...
내 남편은...
I've stayed in many hotels in recent years.
나는 많은 호텔에 머물렀다. 최근 몇 년 동안.
And regarding hotel management knowledge,
그리고 호텔 경영 지식에 관해서는
I haven't let it slip either.
나도 그것을 놓지 않았습니다.
What kind of hotels have you stayed in?
어떤 종류의 호텔에 묵으셨나요?
Many.
많은.
Like Aman in Japan
일본의 Aman처럼
and Banyan Tree in Morocco.
그리고 모로코의 반얀트리.
Also...
또한...
[Xiaoma Hotel]
[샤오마 호텔]
Hampton by Hilton
햄튼 바이 힐튼
and Fairfield by Marriott.
그리고 페어필드 바이 메리어트.
Even budget hotels
저렴한 호텔도
like Home Inn and Hanting,
Home Inn이나 Hanting과 마찬가지로
I've stayed in them too.
나도 그 안에 머물렀어요.
I know your concerns.
나는 당신의 우려를 알고 있습니다.
In terms of work experience,
업무 경험 측면에서
I am indeed lacking.
나는 참으로 부족하다.
So I am willing to start from the basics
그래서 기초부터 시작하겠습니다
and I will work hard to catch up.
그리고 나는 따라잡기 위해 열심히 노력할 것이다.
Here,
여기,
we actually value
우리는 실제로
practical business skills.
실용적인 비즈니스 기술.
If we let you start right away,
지금 바로 시작하게 된다면
can you handle it?
당신은 그것을 처리할 수 있습니까?
I can.
나는 할 수 있다.
[Xiaoma Hotel]
[샤오마 호텔]
Welcome to the team.
팀에 오신 것을 환영합니다.
Am I hired just like that?
나도 그렇게 고용된 걸까?
What about the salary and benefits?
급여와 복지는 어떻습니까?
The position you interviewed for
당신이 인터뷰한 직위
has already been filled.
이미 채워졌습니다.
However,
그러나
we can transfer you to a sales position.
당신을 영업직으로 옮겨드릴 수 있습니다.
This position is commission-based.
이 직위는 커미션 기반입니다.
The base salary is 3,500 yuan a month.
기본급은 월 3,500위안이다.
Is that acceptable to you?
당신이 받아들일 수 있는 일인가요?
I see.
알겠어요.
Ms. Xu,
쉬 선생님,
your competitive advantage is not obvious,
당신의 경쟁 우위는 분명하지 않습니다.
and you have a 10-year gap in your work experience.
그리고 넌 10년 남았어 업무 경험의 공백.
Given your current qualifications,
귀하의 현재 자격을 고려하면,
this is the best offer we can make.
이것이 우리가 할 수 있는 최선의 제안입니다.
[Xiaoma Hotel Labor Contract]
[샤오마 호텔 근로 계약]
Can I get a 2-month advance on my salary?
급여를 2개월치 미리 받을 수 있나요?
You can't get an advance during probation.
보호관찰 기간 동안에는 선지급을 받을 수 없습니다.
I'm really in a tight spot.
저는 정말 곤경에 빠졌습니다.
Tell you what,
말해봐,
we happen to have a client today.
오늘 우연히 고객이 왔습니다.
If you go and win him over,
가서 그를 이기면
the bonus is 5,000.
보너스는 5,000입니다.
How do I win him over?
어떻게 그를 설득할 수 있나요?
Ms. Xu,
쉬 선생님,
you have to figure out how to work on your own.
당신은 알아내야 해 스스로 일하는 방법.
Then please send me the client's information.
그럼 보내주세요 클라이언트의 정보.
Okay.
좋아요.
Hello?
안녕하세요?
Mr. Mai, I've arrived.
마이씨, 도착했어요.
Where are you?
어디세요?
I... I can't hear you.
나... 안 들려요.
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
Hello?
안녕하세요?
You wanted to see me?
나를 보고 싶었나요?
Qiaoqi.
Qiaoqi.
We've only been dating for a month.
우리 사귄 지 딱 한 달 됐어요.
You can't just break up with me like that.
너 나랑 그렇게 헤어지면 안 돼.
If I did something wrong,
내가 뭔가 잘못했다면
-Tell me. I can... -Stop. Stop.
-말해 주세요. 난 할 수 있어... -그만해. 멈추다.
I'll make it short.
짧게 말하겠습니다.
I don't do long-term relationships.
나는 장기적인 관계를 맺지 않습니다.
Getting back together is absolutely impossible.
다시 모이는 중 절대 불가능합니다.
If you really need something in the future,
정말 필요한 경우 미래에 뭔가
you're always welcome to find me.
저를 찾아오시면 언제든지 환영입니다.
But if you try to harass me,
하지만 나를 괴롭히려고 하면
I'll pull all your hair out.
당신의 머리카락을 모두 뽑아 드릴게요.
Hello? What?
안녕하세요? 무엇?
Over here.
여기요.
Mr. Mai.
마이 씨.
-I'm with Xiaoma Hotel... -I've been waiting for you.
-저는 샤오마 호텔에 있어요... -나는 당신을 기다리고 있었어요.
Have a seat.
앉으세요.
Ms. Xu.
쉬 씨.
Actually, you can make money
사실 넌 돈을 벌 수 있어
off me so easily.
너무 쉽게 나에게서 떨어져.
Finish this drink, and I'll sign.
이 잔을 다 마시고 사인을 할게요.
Finish it.
끝내세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
Great!
엄청난!
Good drinker.
좋은 술꾼.
Impressive.
인상적인.
You can really hold your liquor, Ms. Xu.
정말 술을 참을 수 있어요, Xu 씨.
Great.
엄청난.
Ms. Xu, please...
쉬 씨, 제발...
We all came out to have fun.
우리는 모두 재미있게 놀러 나왔어요.
No need to be so shy.
너무 부끄러워할 필요는 없습니다.
I'm actually very gentle.
나는 실제로 매우 온화합니다.
You're unbelievable!
당신은 믿을 수 없어요!
How dare you push me!
감히 나를 밀어내다니!
Didn't your mother ever tell you not to hit women?
네 엄마는 그렇지 않았니? 여자 때리지 말라고 한 적 있어?
What are you standing around for?
당신은 무엇을 위해 서 있습니까?
Get them!
가져와!
Let's go.
갑시다.
Darn it!
젠장!
What's going on with you, Xu Miyu?
무슨 일이에요, 쉬미유?
Instead of staying at home,
집에 있는 대신
you came here to drink with clients?
손님이랑 술 마시러 왔나요?
Do you think this is a game?
이게 게임이라고 생각하시나요?
I got divorced.
나는 이혼했다.
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
Wait.
기다리다.
What exactly happened?
정확히 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
I got divorced.
나는 이혼했다.
I have nothing left.
나는 아무것도 남지 않았습니다.
Then...
그럼...
About your divorce,
이혼에 관해
do your parents know?
부모님은 아시죠?
I wouldn't dare tell them.
나는 그들에게 감히 말하지 않을 것입니다.
In their eyes,
그들의 눈에는
I finally found a good man to marry,
드디어 결혼할 좋은 남자를 찾았어요
so they can stop worrying about me
그들이 나에 대해 걱정하지 않도록
and enjoy a good life.
그리고 좋은 삶을 즐기세요.
If I tell them I'm divorced now
내가 지금 이혼했다고 말하면
and still haven't found a job,
그리고 아직도 일자리를 구하지 못했어요.
how can they hold their heads high in the town?
그들은 어떻게 버틸 수 있는가? 그 사람들이 마을에 머리를 높이 들고 있다고요?
Xu Miyu.
쉬미유.
You know what I've hated most about you
내가 당신에 대해 가장 싫어했던 것이 무엇인지 아시나요
since we were kids?
우리 어렸을 때부터?
You only care about what others think
당신은 다른 사람들이 어떻게 생각하는지에만 관심이 있어요
and never think about yourself.
그리고 절대로 자신에 대해 생각하지 마세요.
You finally have your freedom now.
이제 드디어 자유를 얻었습니다.
Can you please care more about yourself?
자신에 대해 좀 더 관심을 가져주실 수 있나요?
You're right.
당신 말이 맞아요.
That's what I was thinking too.
나도 그렇게 생각하고 있었어요.
So lately,
그래서 최근에는
I've been trying hard to find a hotel job.
나는 호텔 일자리를 구하려고 열심히 노력해 왔습니다.
I want to
난 하고 싶어
go back to 10 years ago,
10년 전으로 돌아가
to the turning point that changed my life,
내 인생을 바꾼 전환점으로
and see if, through my own efforts,
그리고 내 노력으로
I can realize my own value.
나는 나 자신의 가치를 깨달을 수 있다.
That's the spirit.
그것이 바로 정신입니다.
But if you want a hotel job,
하지만 호텔 일자리를 원한다면
why didn't you tell me?
왜 나한테 말하지 않았어?
Didn't I tell you last time
지난번에 내가 말하지 않았나요
that I work at Purong Hotel?
내가 푸롱 호텔에서 일한다고요?
Why would Purong Hotel hire me?
푸롱호텔이 왜 나를 고용할까요?
I'm not qualified.
나는 자격이 없습니다.
A famous 5-star hotel in Shanghai.
상하이의 유명한 5성급 호텔입니다.
I can't even reach it on my tiptoes.
발끝에도 닿지 않네요.
If you can't reach it,
도달할 수 없다면
why don't you get a ladder?
왜 사다리를 가져오지 않니?
I am your ladder.
나는 당신의 사다리입니다.
It's just that
그냥 그래요
your ex-husband is in the tourism industry.
너의 전남편 관광산업에 종사하고 있습니다.
He'll inevitably deal with Purong.
그는 필연적으로 푸롱을 상대하게 될 것이다.
If you really join Purong,
정말 푸롱에 가입하셨다면
and in case
그리고 만약에
you guys run into each other,
너희들은 서로 마주쳤어,
you need to be mentally prepared.
정신적으로 준비가 되어 있어야 합니다.
I don't care.
나는 상관하지 않는다.
I just want to do what I want to do right now.
난 그냥하고 싶어 내가 지금 하고 싶은 일.
I'm relieved to hear that.
그 말을 들으니 안심이 되네요.
Our hotel's marketing department
우리 호텔 마케팅 부서
has an interview tomorrow.
내일 면접이 있어요.
I've referred you.
나는 당신을 추천했습니다.
Someone will add you on WeChat later.
나중에 누군가가 귀하를 WeChat에 추가할 것입니다.
Remember to accept it.
그것을 받아들이는 것을 잊지 마십시오.
Thank you, Qiaoqi.
고마워요, 차오치님.
I will definitely work hard.
나는 반드시 열심히 일할 것이다.
It's just a small favor.
그것은 단지 작은 호의일 뿐입니다.
I can't just shove you in there.
나는 당신을 거기에 밀어 넣을 수 없습니다.
I already feel like
벌써부터 기분이 좋아
I'm getting something for nothing.
나는 공짜로 뭔가를 얻고 있어요.
You didn't get something for nothing.
당신은 아무것도 아무것도 얻지 못했습니다.
You just lost too much.
당신은 너무 많은 것을 잃었습니다.
Good thing you cut your losses in time.
시간이 지나면 손실을 줄일 수 있어서 다행입니다.
From now on,
이제부터
it'll all be good days.
모두 좋은 날이 될 거예요.
From now on, it'll all be good days.
이제부터 모두 좋은 날이 될 거예요.
Cheers.
건배.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Mr. Yang, what's wrong?
양 씨, 무슨 일이에요?
Are you off work?
퇴근 중이신가요?
Yes, I am.
네, 그렇습니다.
But don't worry.
하지만 걱정하지 마세요.
I've already made an appointment with tomorrow's client.
나는 이미 약속을 잡았어요 내일의 고객과 함께.
He'll come to the company in the afternoon to go over the contract.
그 사람은 오후에 회사에 올 거예요 계약을 검토하기 위해.
Okay, okay.
알았어, 알았어.
Stop talking.
말을 중지하세요.
Come to the company tomorrow,
내일 회사로 오세요
hand over the clients you have,
당신이 가지고 있는 고객을 넘겨주세요
and don't come to work anymore.
그리고 더 이상 회사에 오지 마세요.
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
You're asking me?
나한테 묻는 거야?
I've lost all my face because of you.
너 때문에 내 얼굴이 다 망가졌어.
The video of Mrs. Nie at the banquet
니에 부인의 연회 영상
talking about you being a mistress
네가 여주인이라는 얘기를 하는 중
has already reached the clients.
이미 고객에게 도달했습니다.
How dare you stay at the hotel?
감히 호텔에 묵을 수 있나요?
Don't you care about Yuhua's reputation?
Yuhua의 평판에 관심이 없나요?
Come handle your resignation tomorrow.
내일 와서 사직서를 처리하세요.